edreams.com.au 2019-03-08

# Review our site's privacy policy - eDreams AU

We use cookies and share your info with third parties to customise advertising, analyse traffic and provide social media related services. By using our website you accept our Cookies Policy. [Click here to know more. ](https://www.edreams.com.au/cookie-policy/)

﻿ 

  1. __ Who is the Data Controller for your personal data?
  2. __ Why do we collect your personal data?
  3. __ How long do we keep your data?
  4. __ What are the legal grounds for processing your personal data?
  5. __ Who are going to be the recipients of your personal data?
  6. __ What are your Data Rights?

## Who is the Data Controller for your personal data?

**Vacaciones eDreams, SL** (sole shareholding company), with VAT number ESB61965778 and registered address at c/ Conde de Peñalver, 5, 1º Ext. Izq., 28006 Madrid, Spain.

## Why do we collect your personal data?

During the purchase process, we ask you only for **the personal data that we need** to provide you with our mediation services to contract travel products, as well as to attend you and solve any post-contractual query, claim or request.

When you make a reservation for someone else through this website, we will request personal information and travel preferences about that individual. You should obtain the consent of other individuals prior to providing us with their personal information and travel preferences, as any access to view or change their information will be available only through your account.

When you book a trip with us, we subscribe you to our **newsletters** , unless you say otherwise before confirming your booking. Anyway, you will be able to unsubscribe at any moment, using the link that you will find in every newsletter for this purpose.

If you provide us with your **contact email address** , but then you are unable to finish your booking, we use it to contact you in a personalized manner and help you to book your trip, if you are still interested. We also keep it to recognize you when you visit our website again, in order to improve your user experience.

When you visit our Website, we may automatically collect certain **information from your device** (such as IP address, browser type, internet service providers, geographic location, technical information about the device, the time and duration of request and visit, the method used to submit the request to the server). Please note that we may associate this information with your account.

We use this information, as well as the personal data provided defined hereinafter, and share it with third parties, to customize advertising, analyze traffic, provide you with social media related services, improve quality and tailor your searches, to prevent and detect fraud; where some of them, such as payment providers and financial institutions (fraud detection, prevention or chargeback purposes) could be acting as autonomous data controllers.

Some of this information may be collected by using **cookies** or similar tracking technology. For more information, please check our Cookies Policy.

If you sign up for our website using your social media account, link your account on our website to your social media account, or use certain other social media features of ours, we may access information about you via that social media provider in accordance with the provider's policies. The information may include your name, email address, profile picture, gender, list of friends, and other information that you authorize us to receive.

You can also share your personal data with us (such as your contact and/or booking details…) for other purposes, for example, when using any chat, call-back or other feature in order to help you to use our website, or with a future or current booking, etc. Please bear in mind that, when using a third party's feature, this third party may act as joint controller or as processor as per its corresponding privacy policy.

We do not make automated decisions based on profiles, beyond the customization of advertising and the legitimate prevention of fraud on the Internet.

## How long do we keep your data?

We will keep your personal data **while we have legal liabilities** in relation to the services we have provided you with.

In addition to the above, if you are subscribed to our newsletters, we will keep your email address for this purpose **until you ask to be unsubscribed**. Moreover, if you provide us with your contact email address, but then you are unable to finish your booking, we will keep your email address only temporarily and, in any case, for a **maximum period of 15 months**.

The information collected by our cookies is also kept for a **maximum period of 15 months**.

## What are the legal grounds for processing your personal data?

The collection and processing of your personal data are mainly based on the **contractual relationship** you have with us.

When we send our newsletters to you or we use your email address to contact you in a personalized manner or to recognize you when you visit our website again, this is based on our **legitimate interest** in providing you with our services.

The processing of the information collected by our cookies is based on the **consent** provided under the applicable laws.

## Who are going to be the recipients of your personal data?

In order to provide you with our services, we need to communicate your personal data to the **Travel Providers involved** , in order that they can provide you with the products or services you have requested, i.e. the airline which has to issue your ticket and/or operate your flight, the hotel you have booked, the car rental company you have contracted through our Website, etc., as well as those other parties to which it is necessary to disclose your personal data in order to provide you with the requested services in a diligent manner, which will be operating as autonomous data controllers.

We will also share your personal data with third-party companies (including the **eDreams ODIGEO Group** for internal purposes relating to management centralization). In particular, the eDreams ODIGEO Group centralizes the processing of personal data through the Spanish subsidiary eDreams International Network, SL and has adequate internal policies to ensure that any data processing carried out by third parties is made under the strictest security requirements and according to the applicable laws.

Our third-party service providers process your personal data on our behalf and under our instructions for the purposes described hereinabove, acting as data processors or acting as autonomous data controllers (such as those providing us with IT and hosting services, customer support, analytics, payment and financial service providers for chargeback, fraud detection, prevention purposes…). Where third-party service providers have access to data they will only collect information as needed to perform their functions. They are not permitted to share or use the information for any other incompatible purpose.

The transmission of personal data as described herein may include overseas transfers of personal data to countries whose data protection laws are not as comprehensive as those of the countries within the European Union. We shall transfer personal data to recipients offering an adequate level of data protection. In these situations, as may be required, we make contractual arrangements to ensure that your personal data is still protected in line with European standards.

## What are your Data Rights?

Under the General Regulation (EU) 2016/679, of 27 April 2016, on Data Protection ( **GDPR** ), the following rights are recognised in relation to the processing of your personal data:

  1. **Right of access.** You have the right to confirm that your personal data is being processed and, if the case, to get a copy of such data and complete information about the processing.
  2. **Right to rectification.** You have the right to amend errors, modify data that may be inaccurate or incomplete and ensure the information which is being processed is right.
  3. **Right to erasure.** You have the right to suppress your data without undue delay in the case that the processing is illegal or that the purpose for processing or collecting it has disappeared.
  4. **Right to restriction.** You have the right to ask for the suspension of the processing in the case that such processing is illegal or inadequate.
  5. **Right to object.** You have the right to object to the processing of your data in the case that the purpose of the processing is direct marketing or that the processing should be stopped for reasons relating to your personal situation, unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds to continue processing them or that the processing is necessary to exercise or defend legal claims.
  6. **Right not to be subject to automated individual decisions.** You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or similarly affects you, unless that is necessary for the execution of a contract, is permitted by the Law or it is based on your explicit consent.

Based on the nature of our services and the purpose of the collection and the processing of your personal data, the _Right to portability_ is not applicable.

In order to exercise your rights, please, send an email to [dpo@edreamsodigeo.com](mailto:dpo@edreamsodigeo.com) or send your request by post courier to the following address: Data Protection – Paseo Zona Franca, 195-205, 08038 Barcelona, Spain. In your request, you have to clearly state (i) your personal identity, by indicating your complete name and the email address you used to purchase or create an account, and (ii) the right or rights you are exercising.

You can also ask the Spanish Authority on Data Protection ([www.agpd.es](http://www.agpd.es/)) for protection to ensure that your rights are respected, if you wish.

The exercise of these rights is free of charge, unless you make unjustified or excessive requests. In this case, we will be entitled to charge you with a reasonable fee based on administrative costs.

? 

Yes, we are all residents from... 

  * If some passengers are residents and others are not, you must book separately. 
  * eDreams will automatically apply the prices with the corresponding discount for residents. You will have to provide the necessary information to prove your residence. 

S

 flights found for your search 

Return 

One way 

Multi-city 

Add another flight  (tailor your trip with up to 3 flights) 

Up to 40% off your hotel when you book now! 

Location

Distance from city centre: 

Search  Search Flight + Hotel 

F

Sorry, we were not able to access the requested page. 

\- If you have typed in the address manually, please make sure it is correct. \- If you have clicked on a link to get here, there is probably an error in the link \- If you have reached this site by clicking on another link, it is possible that the session expired
